commonsensewithmoney.com 2018-03-23

# Privacy Policy - Common Sense With Money

We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using our web site. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information that may be collected by us on our site. This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. Our Privacy Policy is as follows:

**1\. Collection of Data.**  
Our registration process requires only a valid e-mail address and a unique user ID and password. Providing us with other information is at your option. Please take note that your user name, e-mail address, or other submissions that you make on this site may contain your real name or other personally identifiable information and, as a result, may appear on this site. Like many web sites, we may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files such as your IP address and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site is set forth below.

**2\. Use of Data.**  
We may use personal information to customize and improve your user experience on this site. We will make efforts so that your personal information will not be provided to third parties. In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites.

**3\. Cookies.**  
Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings.

**4\. Editing or Deleting Your Account Information.**  
We provide you with the ability to edit the information in your user account information that you provided to us in registration. You may request deletion of your user account by contacting us. Content or other data that you may have provided to us and that is not contained within your user account, such as posts that may appear within our forums, may continue to remain on our site at our discretion even though your user account is deleted.

**5\. Changes to this Privacy Policy.**  
We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.

**6\. NO GUARANTEES.**  
While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of personal information and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of personal information.

**7\. Contact Information.**  
If you have any questions about this Policy or our web site, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.commonsensewithmoney.com/contact-me/).
